- Okay, you're sending an email update
-好吧，你要發送電子郵件更新
to your close teammates.
給你的親密隊友。
You might try opening with, "HEY, TEAM!" an emoji,
您可以嘗試以「嘿，團隊！」開頭。一個表情符號
and if your me, maybe throw in a corny dad joke
，如果你是我的話，也許會給他們一個不錯的爸爸笑
to try and keep them engaged.
話來嘗試讓他們參與。
Now, that same email might not land so well
現在，同樣的電子郵件可能不
with, say, your CEO or a new client.
適合您的首席執行官或新客戶。
Kind of makes you cringe, right?
有點讓你躲起來，對吧？
Now obviously messages need to be tailored
現在顯然，消息需要根據接
to the person receiving them.
收它們的人量身定制。
Your CEO might just need a quick bullet-point summary,
您的首席執行官可能只需要快速的項目摘要，但另一
but your client, on the other hand,
方面，您的客戶可能需要更多的
might need more reassurance and detailed solutions.
保證和詳細的解決方案。
Without help from AI, crafting several versions
如果沒有 AI 的幫助，製作相同消
of the same message could take hours.
息的多個版本可能需要數小時。
Not everyone is a professional writer,
並非每個人都是專業作家
and it can be challenging to adjust your writing style
，因此對於不同受
to different audiences.
眾調整您的寫作風格可能很有挑戰。
It's also pretty common to get lost in endless rewrites.
在無盡的重寫中迷路也很常見。
All this, and you still need
所有這些，您仍然需
to make sure your core message comes through.
要確保您的核心信息傳達。
Getting your communication just right is vital,
讓您的溝通更正確是至關
and that's because you're doing more
重要的，這是因為您不僅
than just trying to share information.
僅僅是嘗試分享信息。
You're trying to achieve an objective.
你正在嘗試實現一個目標。
But if someone misunderstands your message or your tone,
但是，如果有人誤解您的訊息或您的聲音，
you could lose their trust,
您可能會失去他們的信
and that can lead to more questions, more meetings,
任，這可能會導致更多問題、更多會議
and more reviews.
和更多評論。
Things can get pretty slow, inefficient,
事情可能會變得非常慢，效率低，
and draining real fast.
而且耗盡快。
But with Gemini, you have a writing partner
但是，有了 Gemini，您有一個寫作夥伴，
that can help you produce multiple tailored email drafts
可以幫助您在
in just seconds.
幾秒鐘內製作多個量身定制的電子郵件草稿。
In this course you'll learn how to use AI
在本課程中，您將學習如何使用 AI
to amplify the impact of your communication.
來擴大溝通的影響。
We'll show you how you can combine your own voice
我們將向您展示如何將自己的聲音
and judgment with AI's power to help you generate,
和判斷力與 AI 的力量結合，以幫助您產生
refine, and practice communication.
、改進和練習溝通。
Of course, the principles
當然，有效溝通
of effective communication are still timeless.
的原則仍然是永恆的。
Things like knowing your audience
如認識受眾
and delivering messaging effectively, they still matter.
和有效傳遞消息等事情，仍然很重要。
But now we can use AI to deliver on those principles
但現在，我們可以使用 AI 以
in a brand-new way.
全新的方式實現這些原則。
Specifically your role is to bring your strategic thinking
具體而言，您的角色是將您的戰略
and your emotional intelligence to the table.
思維和情緒智能帶到桌面上。
Here are five communication elements
以下是您的角色至關
where your role is essential.
重要的五個溝通元素。
The first is purpose and intent.
第一個是目的和意圖。
This is all about defining the why
這一切都是關於定義
or what you want your message to do.
您希望消息做的原因或什麼。
For example, do you wanna persuade, to inform,
例如，你想說服、提供資訊、降低
deescalate, or inspire?
升級或激勵？
The second element is understanding your audience.
第二個要素是了解您的受眾。
Only you understand the priorities of your leadership,
只有您了解領導的優先順序，
your clients' needs, and your team's mindset.
客戶的需求和團隊的思維。
Without you, AI won't know the context
沒有您，AI 將無法知道您
and history of your relationship with your audience.
與受眾關係的背景和歷史。
Next is authenticity and voice.
接下來是真實性和聲音。
You wanna make sure that any communication coming
你想確保任何來自你的溝通
from you sounds authentically like you.
聽起來都像你一樣
You're the final editor
您是最終編輯者，
that makes sure your message matches your personal
確保您的訊息與您的個人
or company brand and values.
或公司品牌和價值觀相符。
Then there's accountability.
然後還有責任。
Keep in mind that you're responsible
請記住，對您的單詞可能
for the impact your words may have
會產生的影響以及它們可
and any consequences they may bring,
能帶來的任何後果負責，
so be sure to read every word.
因此請務必閱讀每個單詞。
Finally, there's strategic judgment.
最後，還有戰略判斷。
Use your experience and your wisdom
運用您的經驗和智慧
to choose a type of communication that works best,
來選擇最適合的溝通類型，例
like an email versus a phone call,
如電子郵件與電話，
or in some cases, no message at all.
或在某些情況下，完全沒有消息。
So what is AI's role in this partnership?
那麼 AI 在這個合作夥伴關係中的角色是什麼？
Well, you can use AI as a thought partner
好吧，您可以在構
while you build your communication strategy,
建溝通策略的同時使用 AI 作為思想夥伴，
and you can have it tackle time-consuming tasks.
並且可以讓它處理耗時的任務。
Let's look at a few areas
讓我們來看一下
where AI can help you reach your goals.
AI 可以幫助您實現目標的幾個領域。
First is brainstorming.
第一是腦力激盪。
You can describe a communication scenario,
您可以描述溝通情境，例
like how to position a new service for clients
如如何為客戶定位新服務
or how to share disappointing news.
或如何分享令人失望的新聞。
Then Gemini can provide you
然後，雙子座可
with options and thought starters
以在評估如何處理情況
as you evaluate how to approach the situation.
時為您提供選擇和思考初學者。
Next is rapid drafting and variation.
接下來是快速製圖和變化。
Sometimes the hardest thing is starting from a blank page.
有時最難的事情就是從空白頁開始。
Within Gemini, Canvas can create multiple versions
在 Gemini 中，Canvas 可以在幾
and key talking points in seconds.
秒鐘內創建多種版本的通信，例如商務電子郵件，一頁文檔和關鍵討論點。
And it can tailor all of them to different audiences.
而且它可以為不同的受眾量身定制所有它們。
Now we have something to work from.
現在我們有什麼要去處理。
A third area is refinement and polish.
第三個領域是細緻和拋光。
Gemini can help you improve your message.
雙子座可以幫助您改善信息。
It can instantly rephrase something to make it more clear.
它可以立即重寫一些內容以使其更清晰。
It can also adjust your tone of voice from formal to casual,
它還可以將您的聲音從正式調整到休閒，並
and it can provide feedback on your work as you iterate.
且可以在您迭代時對您的工作提供反饋。
The last area is practice and simulation.
最後一個領域是練習和模擬。
You can rehearse a sales meeting
您可以
or difficult conversation using Gemini Live,
使用 Gemini Live 排練銷售會議或困難的對話，這
and this can help you build confidence
可以幫助您在
before the actual conversation happens.
實際對話發生之前建立信心。
Now you'll notice that I didn't list ghostwriter
現在你會注意到，我沒有列出鬼寫作者在
under AI's responsibilities,
AI 的職責下，
and that's because if you completely rely on AI,
這是因為如果你完全依賴 AI，
it might result in communication
這可能會導致溝通
that's missing important context
缺少重要背景
or just doesn't feel authentic.
或感覺不真實。
Remember, you are and your voice are essential
請記住，您是，您的聲音對於這個方程
to the equation.
是必不可少的。
Instead, you can use AI to speed up the editing process
相反，您可以使用 AI 加快編輯過程，以
to help bring your voice to life.
幫助您的聲音變得生動。
It can help give your wild ideas structure
它可以幫助您賦予瘋狂的想法結構
or help you get past that dreaded blank page.
，或幫助您超越可怕的空白頁面。
You might spend less time struggling
您可能會花更少的時間在
with how to say something
如何說話上努力，
and more time improving what you wanna say.
而且更多時間改善您想說的內容。
When you use AI in the right way,
當您以正確的方式使用 AI 時，
you can get closer to the action
您可以更接近想通
or reaction you wanna achieve with your communication.
過溝通實現的行動或反應。
You'll find that your emails actually get read,
您會發現您的電子郵件實際上被閱讀
and people will follow through.
，並且人們會跟踪。
Or your communication is clearer,
或者，您的溝通更清晰，
reducing back-and-forth and getting to quicker decisions.
減少來回並更快地做出決策。
And maybe your perspective is better understood
也許您的團
by your teammates or clients,
隊成員或客戶更好地理解您的觀點
and as a result, you'll be more effective in informing
，因此您將更有效地通知他們的意見，
or even changing their opinions.
甚至更改他們的意見。
So let's get rid of those long, confusing email threads
因此，讓我們擺脫那些漫長而令人困惑的電子郵件線程
and start communicating more clearly.
，並開始更清楚地溝通。